Hello hello everyone welcome back to my channel
keep creating friends in today's first video
we
saw the important news and indicators of weekly market flats the
United Nations report has said
that the global economy will contract by 4.5 percent this year
so the entire world economy will
show a negative growth of 14% and you know
how uncertain the situation is for the banking sector in India
until a
decision on loan moratorium interest is taken
by the Supreme Court so keeping
all these news and
indicators in mind which
fundamentals should you currently consider
for investing
and which ones can you do at the graduation level
we will discuss that in this video
before starting the video let me
tell you that if you have not subscribed to the channel till now then
this machine love you all information
and ideas about investing and wealth
creation your subscriptions likes and comments give
me more motivation  I get it and I keep
trying to make videos on your suggested topics as well, so just hit the
like button and
thank the channel and get notifications of Pallav
Namak Puri so that
you do not miss out on the upcoming new videos. You
can also follow us on Facebook, Twitter and Telegram
so that the links for your knowledge and glance are
given in the description. So without
taking any more fear time, let's get
started friends, our first stock today
is the country's largest and best private
bank giver, HDFC Bank. Its market
capitalization is around Rs 5 lakh 75 thousand
crore. Depends upon 242, it
is a little less, we have also talked about it in all our previous videos
that RBI has told the bank, so do
not go on a different path right now, preserve your guest
teachers because there is a lot of uncertainty right now,
regarding the residual
payment of loss recording appears in the,
hence Upadhyay's regulation of being
detected, there will be a little less sales, but it is a
very solve fundamental, very good
company, that is why I think that  In
future, this lead can also be good and handsome,
son, its beta is 1.00, so for those who are watching our videos for the
first time, who are new
to our channel, let me tell you that if the beta is
more than 54, then we understand that
that particular topic, that specific beta should be a
little higher than the overall market
and beta which is less than one is an
indicator, it tells that that
specific beta should be a little lower than the overall market,
so this beta is 1.06, son, you
can understand that since it is a
stock of the financial sector, then its real quality will be
that and it will be a little higher than the market, so
son, the speed of the stock of the financial sector is a
little higher than channel one, the
speed of the industry is around 2014
and you are
getting this at a low valuation of the industry, you have a discount,
so this shows you how good
and percentage can be if you invest in it, then you can get
investment in India's
best private bank, Walt Bank of India, at a
salary lower than the industry valuation.  You are getting delivery
percentage parties percentage that
shows you how handsome delivery people
are clear in their investment account,
people are taking delivery of it in their long term investment account that if we
talk about its Christ then it is
not bad for investment at the current price level,
if you get this Schezwan anywhere
and you are selecting that can for long-term interest in it,
then that
price level can be good, we have brought it for long-term
interest in it, want to wait a bit
and especially care as we
talked about in the beginning of the video that the
decision of the Supreme Court is going to come on Monday
or anytime, their decision is going to come
that the interest on the loan moratorium will be
waived or how it will be
compensated, so a decision is going to come on that
and the loan auditorium which was extended
till Sector-28 is also
ending on Monday, but all this uncertainty,
all this instability remains
in the banking sector, so I want to look at it a little,
you want to understand whether its
reservation is how  It is done if you
want to wait a little and if
any decision comes in this, I don't know whether it will
depend on your side Tuesday
how the decision comes, but if there is a
dance end in this topic and if this move is
found at the level of 800 to 900, then it can be a very
good level, this powerful, this
strong fundamentals,
our second stock number from flour to lift the Play Store
and I want to tell you one more thing
that we have been using this tool for a long time,
looking at the metrics of any stock and looking at its price
movement, price labels, so whatever
we are going to discuss here in this box is
fundamentally a very big part, aka, a
separate system of all these stocks, in
which we will see by commenting on many
metrics, many international and
historical places, so I will
separate them in one video, otherwise
this video will become very long, already
actually in today's video we are going to cover so many
stocks that  You see,
I'll cover that quickly
because I have so many things to talk about.
Otherwise, the video could be very long.
So, we'll take an overview of the price levels of all the stocks in the past
and their fundamental metrics. So,
you can see it in the room. But
in the general insurance sector, the number one company in
India, in terms of private players, is a good company with very soft fundamentals.
Its market
price is around 1500. Its market price is around 1500. The decline
point is where it is. As
we saw, the stocks in the financial sector have
not seen much increase in the appointed percentage, but
these will be considered lower middle. So, that's the
point below which shows you that the
overbought period is slightly less than the market.
Another objective within the finance sector has
also been discussed in previous videos
that the life insurance and
general insurance related stocks are
slightly less volatile than the market.
Even when the finance sector has some money, there are
some tractors which are
slightly less volatile than the market. So, channel
insurance, life insurance, etc. will be market
today quality.  Its beta
point note is around the back gate of the industry
and you are getting this at a little Addison premium
calculation flight.
Delivery percentage is a very handsome delivery percentage of sixty percent to the delivery percentage.
This shows
that at this price level rise, people are
taking delivery at their level. If you get this stock at the
level of 1285 to 13, then this could be a good level
for long-term interest.
But if you want to wait a little for the
Supreme Court decision and subscription to
start and then
invest in it, then if you want to invest
in this stock, then HDFC AMC comes in at a
level of 1100 to 1150, then that could be an even better
level for investing in stocks.
HDFC AMC is the number one stock in terms
of state players and it belongs to the
most reputed in India. So,
I find its fundamentals to be very strong. If you have an interest in investing in a
long-term asset management company, then
HDFC AMC is the
number one choice.  Maybe for you, the market
upside for the licensed company is around 45 thousand crores, with an
average of 21.33, respectfully in the
left 6.7 percent, taking much less voltage than the market.
In this sentence, there has been a lot of
quality in it and it is doing a lot of dancing. So
by looking at the chart, you will feel that
before the market, but overall, if we talk about long-term Everest, then
its beta will still
get less votes than the market. So, this shows you that from an office
point of fundamental, due to near-term quality, a
lot of dance will be seen in it.
We will also see it after this. But overall, if it is said over a long period of time, its quality remains less than the market. The speed of the industry is 2017 and you were getting it on a lot of prevention earlier. I remember that it used to be
around PCO, but now
due to the price correction in it, its price has
reduced a lot and its
premium on Sanjeev and Industries has
reduced a lot. So, you will get a few females
of 135. People have complained about the Industries price.
Very respectable delivery of 6-7 percent.
Percentage and this shows
how much conviction investors have in it,
how attractive investors are finding it at this price level.
Talking about its price level, if you get it around Karna juice current
price, then that is also
good for long term investment.
If you
want to wait a little more, if you
get it around 2006, at the level of 2000 to 2050, then
what can I say, it is a
very soft middle company for the long term, which is best to
avoid. You should
not buy this date. My other point is that if you
look at its solid fundamentals now and
you feel that this app management press
mutual fund business is not going anywhere and
you see long term growth, then
HDFC AMC is one of the best
players in the management computer market.
Our next topic is
Tech Mahindra Bank. HDFC Bank has as
solid fundamentals as Kotak
Mahindra Bank. Its market share is
around 2.5 lakh.  Dhundhu is around Rs 1 crore.
He has not tweeted anything yet.
As you said, due to RBI regulations, the
bank has not yet made any different decision.
Its relation points meter is 1.07, so it is
slightly higher than the market.
These teachers are
still getting good PM vibrations. You can see a
good PM mission because it is such a
solid company that people are behind it. In this piece also,
you can see the delivery percentage is
very decent at 40%.
If we talk about its price level, if
you get it between Rs 1250 to Rs 13, then
it can be a good investment.
Spread around its current market price. If you want to wait a little in it
and want to invest after the patient track, then the
level of Rs 11 to Rs 1150 can be suitable for you.
Nestle India's stock is below the market leader by up to Rs 1 in the SSC business. So, it is the
most fundamentally sound DharmaCG business.
Its market application in India is around Rs
1.5 lakh.  Devi Andher
is very respectable around 2.17%
speed test points, so SMC Business
Office is late market quality which is
also visible here in its beta,
around this industry recommendation, you are
getting some PM valuation celebrity on your, teller percentage is quite
respectable FD center point to point,
miss latest around 15000 percent and if you get
15000 juice current level is around the same,
if you get it at this level then you
can invest in it, this is
not a bad level for the long term, so
you can see that this stock had
reached around 18,000, after reducing from there
it is trending around 15000,
so this is a different level of trading,
but if you want to wait a little
and if in the near term you get
this quality in the market and you
get this stop between 13,000 to 14000 then it can be a very good level
For long-term interest,
our next stock is another such
giant, Hindustan Unilever. Its actual
market capitalization is around Rs 5 lakh
crore. You can see that for such a
big company, its yield is also a very
respectable 1.6 percent.
Its yield is also much less than one. The
industry speed is 6 inches and
you are getting a little premium vibrations
on the back of everyone. The front percentage has a
very strong delivery percentage.
If you get this stock at the level of 2000 to 2050, then it
is enough.
For long-term investment, if you
want to wait a little, then the level of 1968 and 1950 is
very good. It is a very good level for
long-term investment. You
can see here. This top free closed was
trading at 25th and 26th levels. After the
arrested recovery from spoon crust, it
reached the 26th level. Then after racing from there,
it is currently trading in the middle of 2021. So,
in  You can keep both the labels in mind,
whichever of these you are
comfortable with, you can make payment there.
ITC app is
another discus player of CG business and cigarette business,
its market place is in a
free band around 2 lakh crore, tennis is very
excellent, almost around six percent,
watch one or two videos earlier in which
its difference is situated at 4.75 percent,
its price has further corrected,
so definitely add it is possible that it has
increased even more, so almost around six percent
for FD, rather its search and then the
potential which is there for growth prospects in the feature, then the search
is quite excellent, around tips percent, my
tasty point education is much less than the market,
say time of the industry, it is
around 1340, what you are getting on that thing, the
PK of the industry is getting at umpire level
1415, keep delivery percentage is
very handsome, very respectable delivery of 21 percent
is famous  If you
look at the charts, you can invest in it even at the current level,
which is
between its price of 178 and 175. If you
decide among yourselves and look at it a little more and
want to wait a little, then 16755, the price
can also sink to 7. So, this is a
company with fundamentals and is a very positive test
business. In the long term, its sister
business is looking good.
If you can develop conventionally in the stock,
if you think that its
feature potential looks good, then you
can invest in it for the long term.
But let me also say that
you will have to be very patient because your
business is a very
glowing business, it is an established business,
hence you may spend a little more money on advertising and
launching your products and
making a splash there, there may be
some increase against it. In the short
term, you may
not see much upset in the price, but
in the long term, if you can fold it patiently
for the next five years, then
I will definitely buy it personally.  My opinion is that
you can definitely benefit from this in the long run.
HDFC Limited is one of the best companies in India
among the best and CSS and housing finance companies.
Its main consolidation is
around Rs 3 lakh crore. Tubelight is
quite expensive at around 1.27 percent. Its
yield is 1.24 percent, so the order value is slightly higher than the market.
Therefore, whenever there is talk of access,
it is usually a little higher than the market.
Guest of the industry and you are not getting a little
PM valuation on very high specifications
and it was a team of experts
but it is currently trading. The delivery percentage is very
good at 4 percent on almost every person.
This shows how much
confidence people have in the stock of HDFC Limited.
If you want to pick this stop on current affairs level, you can do it. The
level of 16.51 is very different levels. It is a
very good level for long term investment.
But if you want to wait a little
and there can be market volatility.  If you
want to take advantage of it, you
can wait for its level of 1515. If
this stock comes on its strength, then take it in very well,
you can click on a very good level.
If you want to invest in it for Long Samundar Singh, then
Bajaj
Finance is also a very fundamental company.
Rajiv
Jain ji has taken this company from where it was
and its system and process, which is the
system and process of tempered glass,
gives a lot of positive energy. If you buy
Embassy instead of fans, then for the long term,
I think the market can give it a very
good picture. Buy it according to long-term goals
potential. Its market
capitalization is around Rs 1 lakh 90 thousand
crore. Why the demand is not very high, the
contributed equally percentage is that it is a
tile stock with above market value, which
you can see in beta. Here, there is a beta of
1.46. This is a tile stock with above market value,
this is the industry's 2017
and you are getting it at a little free valuation of the party.
Telugu percentage is
not a hand,
almost water line of twenty one percent is okay delivery percentage,
so it shows that you
can also weigh a little on it,
we look at its chart in which you will find
pass double, you
can weigh a little on it and 2627 is the fourth
level, if you are in the market, then that can be a good
level for long-term interest,
if you see this topic potential,
for the future, if you should weigh a little more, you want to show some
patience, you
want to shave quality in the market and
want to increase your stock margin a little, then
if you get this stock
anywhere between 2000 to 2000, then it can be a very
good, very strong level.
For the bank, Dr. Lal Path Lab is the market leader
in the Indian organization's logic loop business, it is a
company with very soft fundamentals, it is a debt-free company,
its retail business, its
business model is very good, very
dead, so it is a company with good fundamentals, it is
a media company, its market place has
around 15 thousand crores.  The day cents
are around point six percent, a
quarter of an inch from the stock, so it is much lower than the market. Do not
forget a very different delivery of 50%. If you get this interest
between 50% and 50%, then
how can you differentiate your investment in it? You may
want to do it for the long term. If you
want to wait a little and that matter is
positive, then if you get it at the level of 15 to 1550, then it can be a
very good
level. There may be some disturbance in the
long-term interest. For chemical
industries related, we have to choose a small cap
stock here.
Recently, there has been so much use about the tune fold,
so much reaction
for retail investors. We discussed it in today's
video, which is the IT Today video, in which we did
our weekly market highlights, we
discussed it in detail in that, in which
I tell you my opinion poll
that my key is open about what ever happened at our time, we
tried in difficulties in this
pick, then on lower circuit.  And circuits are being put on,
now I think that its
bank level companion can be quite attractive, that is why
I have put a spoon shot here so
that you can keep an eye on this topic,
I am keeping it on my voter list, it
is a company with very easy fundamentals, in that video
also we have dispatched that the tips
taken, the offer for sale that has come, is making the long term
potential of the company even
stronger, the fundamentals of the
company are getting even stronger, so you
can invest in it, you can do your
research, you can study a little, you can
convince yourself about this company,
if you like this company for
long term then you can cancel the amendment in it,
this is a small cap company, its
market capitalization is around 5000
crores, the tubewell points are quite low,
Vanshi is currently focusing on her blog
and rallies and shares, that too
on growth, which we also discussed in this morning's video,
internet, so its De
Villiers is a little low, son, if the points
come then it will be as much as the market
You are getting A37 at a very premium valuation in the Wall Tiles and Moh Industry since 2014
and there are two reasons for this, it is a market leader,
in its business act there is glass line that there are
one or two or three companies in India that manufacture fit
and finally after
reaching the decision given to its company,
D International company, its business has been
bought by the jail warden in India, so
now only two distant places are left,
actually Glass Coated which is a
smaller company than Jennifer and take Jail Pot, the current
market share was around 50 to 55
percent but after
acquiring D, then its market share will be
around eight percent, so
when you reverse it in the market leader with eighty percent market share, then
its valuation will get a little cream, along with
HD Last company which is such a competitor,
keep a little moderately high competition for it, along with
shift in Jewel Parlor, explain in detail
its paint company, yes, the company Ford,
its paint company is 2gm  And there is a
joint venture between Federer and ATM debit company,
most of which is buying, so it is
trying to expand its business not only in India but also globally,
so all these factors are
your information, if you feel that
this company shows good prospects,
you see good prospects
for growth, then you
can collect investment in it, the delivery percentage is
showing hundred here because
it has been taking lower circuit after lower circuit for the last two-three days, so
now the real 12%
is 10 because when lower circuit is applied then
you have to do delivery best trading
or you have to do stupid hundred
Cent delivery has to be sold. Here one has to
take hundred percent delivery,
hence its delivery is one and a half. Whenever any
stock has an upper circuit or lower circuit,
you will always see the delivery percentage fund.
You can see it here. There is a
pie chart on this website by following the judgment,
you will see these small dots of
all the lower circuits. Therefore, the
current market price here is right, it is
around 38 top. If you get this stock at the current
level of 3550 rupees, then the
current price is around 200-300 levels. Then
you should definitely consider investing in it.
I think the long-term potential
looks good in this company. It can
fetch a good price, but you should wait a little.
Now you want to see
how the market reacts. Right now, can we
return to lower circuit on this or not?
Now, if there is quality and negative
sentiment about this company, then
if this proposal touches the plateau and if
you get a cheap price here between 150, then
I think it is for the long term.  That
too is very good, that can be done. Now if you
want to exercise a little patience, then
another big share from Britannia to Z is a
very good company. Its
market place is around 90 thousand crores,
deposits are around 9521 percent, a very
respectable diminishing point is its
value which shows that it is much lower than the market,
leadership is around 65 and it is
getting cheaper than the middle of the industry, it is getting
at a discount even compared to the middle of the industry, so this snake is trending on the back of 51,
delivery percentage is different, there
is a respectable delivery percentage of 30 percent in the city, applicant of this
you will see that
if you get anywhere at 35 or 36 level around the current market price, then
for the long term, the price can double. You
see that whatever quality comes in the market,
and CG sectors do not come down that much,
hence I think that you should
probably take it down that much, otherwise, but if it goes down
and if you get it at 32  If it is found at the level of 3250 339 then
it can be a very
good level for investment, you can cancel the investment there.
In the business of gas distribution and natural gas distribution,
like the market in the Mumbai area, there
is almost monopoly of MGL. Its
market application is around 80 crores, it is
a small cap company, right now the price is quite
good, around 14.26 percent, its
deal used to be around that from the price point,
its price has
come down a little more, there is a slight correction in its price level, hence
it has increased a little more, so
if you talk at this level, then
you can get a very good return of about 4.2-6%,
this is a very good handsome dandruff,
from the price point, although the
fitting of Bolt and Jest is much less than the market and
you are also getting a discount from the speed of the industry,
friends,
handsome delivery percentage of every digit percent,
this trick if you  If you get 800 to 600, then it can be a
very good level for the bank,
but if you want to wait a little and
if the market is positive and if you
get this journey i.e. between 7575, then it is a very
good label for long term investment.
Gujarat State Petronet Limited is also
a very good company in gas distribution, with very
soft fundamentals. Its
market place has around 11 thousand crores.
This margin is for all midcap companies. The
denominator is quite good. A respectable 1.03 is the
festival price. You will have an AC point 6. For you, there are
low tiles. The
price of the industry is ten and you are getting almost the same at
9.98 delivery percentage. It is quite
respectable and a
very good delivery of 21 percent is famous.
If you get this stock between 190 to 200, then it is
quite good for investment. It can be
if you want to wait a little and
you want some quality in the market. You can
also be
interested in the near term top level of 17790.  It is a multinational company which is a very strong player in the full white goods
exports which includes washing machines, refrigerators,
microwaves etc.
Whirlpool India is its Indian subsidiary.
So,
I think World Food is a company with very soft fundamentals. Its
market
cap is around 26 thousand crores.
Point to point, the speed is a little less than the
market. The voltage is
around 1297. You are
getting it for free at a price of 1297,
but even at this Paris price level,
people are getting a very good delivery percentage of 50%.
If you get this totka
at the level of 1950 to 2000, then it can be a very
good level for long term
investors. But if you want to wait a little
and at this time, if
you get some quality, then if you get this top apk file at the level of 15017, then you
can get a very good label for the long term.
Avni Supermart, which is also
known as Demand, is a retail business.  I am a very
strong player in debt-free
companies, its promoter and that is
Radhakrishnan Dani, he is a very good business man,
his track record is very good,
so I think Agni Supermart is fundamentally a very
strong company, the
market reflection of Agni Supermart is around 1 lakh
36 thousand crores and
well, it has not given any limit yet
because the tax entry
is focusing on its browser, right now it is an emerging business, it is a
gang business, son, its points are
much lower than the market, the tile
of the industry is 1972,
it is getting straight at a very hype premium valuation right now and
you can get this stock
at a PM valuation of 128, but
even at this premium calculation and at this price
level, people are getting a good delivery of
18 persons, very festival, very
good delivery, famous this trick,
if you get it for 2000 to 2050, then
this can be a very good level for
long-term interest, but if you do a
little  If you want to wait and
see the level of 1819 and a half stopped
in the near future, then you can definitely cancel at that level. It can be
quite excellent and very
attractive for long term
investors. Our last stock of today is the
market leader in the infrastructure segment of India. If you want, you
can call it Larsen & Toubro. Its
market application is around 125000 crores.
This sleep is also quite good.
2.0 2% from one and a half inch, so it is as good as the market. And the
speed of the industry is around ATM. You are
getting some prevention at 21.5,
see the delivery percentage, you understand.
Looking at the excellent delivery percentage of 77 percent, you understand that this is
such a high commission for investors.
Larsen & Toubro has a future
prospect. If you get Valentina stock at the
level of 800 and a half to 900, then it can be a
very good level, as I
saw in January-February, it was around 1460.  It was
trending at the level of 14 years and
you are also getting a good correction
at a good discount, so the
level of 800 to 900 can be a very good test, great
for long term investment, but
if you want to wait a little,
due to minute positivity, if this snake is
found among 750 students, then it can be sold at a very
attractive price for
medium to long term, interesting friends,
today's video will help you in getting clear knowledge, this is the
National Commission, which will bring the right knowledge question to you,
in every upcoming video we will
discuss many interesting topics
and I will keep sharing useful
ideas and thoughts for you, similarly
every weekend we will keep discussing weekly market updates and our
views about the current market situation, so
definitely
subscribe to the channel and if
you like the next video update, then
like the video if you
think that this information can help someone
So share this with your friends and family
members and
subscribe to the channel. In my next video
with job discussion till then
tech institutes will cook this.